I see the girl saying, "Ooh, like you
guys are feeling it, right?"
[music and singing]
>> Of windmills and rockets and empty
baskets. [music]
In [music] my heart is a waterfall.
Bleeding pine trees, lit [music] up
windows, poison arrows.
In my heart [music] is a waterfall.
Silver linings and dirty laundry.
[music]
Here is another Diana vlog. Obviously,
I'm Diana.
My house [music] is
honey.
>> Yes. You hear this? [music]
>> Okay.
[music]
See
how it is.
[music]
We [music] just arrived.
One of the things that I learned is
[music] that your hardships are so
important. Whatever hardship you're
[music] facing is something God is
actively trying to teach [music] you.
God has been actively trying to teach me
to be self-sufficient. [music]
Reason why a lot of times I have faced
[music] disappointments. Disappointments
from people close to me. Most of the
disappointments [music] from the people
that work for me. Like you know I keep
complaining. or my editor this, my
housekeeper that, oh, I [music] brought
somebody to do this, or my photographer
this. God has been teaching me
self-sufficiency, like being able to be
in a very bad situation and get it
together by myself. So, I know that
that's something that has been useful at
points where I could have broken down.
[music]
>> Hi, good afternoon.
[music] Thank you. Oh, okay. Pants do
not fit. That's [music] why I have to
put a belt to gather it together.
Someone's just going to think that's
just fashion, but I got them in a
[music] big size.
But this is cute. This is fancy. I'm
just having conversations with my
assistant, [music] my makeup artist, my
hair stylist, cuz I'm shooting for my
birthday tomorrow.
We are here.
Good afternoon.
Thank you. I'm late for my appointment.
I'm so [music] sorry. Like
>> just sit there.
>> Okay. So, we're going to do the IV now,
right? [music]
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
>> Um, cold. [music]
Thank you.
The last time I came was February. Ever
since, it just feels like life has been
so fast. like I [music] just barely have
time to, you know, come for my EMS
sessions. I'm sure my sister is gonna be
[gasps]
[laughter]
I'm gonna try to dodge her so she
doesn't see me because she's going to be
like Diana like it's been so long. We
had body goals. We had a plan and you
didn't stick out to the plan. But yeah,
I'm currently seeing this series. It's
called My Life with the Walter Boys, I
think. And I've been enjoying it. It's
kind of like my comfort show, something
I can watch while working.
You guys know I barely ever watch TV.
Like, and it's been fun. It just gives
me this, you know, add-on to my life.
Like, my life is serious. I can watch I
can do a little bit of high school drama
and a little bit of mushiness, a little
bit of a and all that. It just [music]
gives me that little comfort feeling
when I'm getting onto my busy busy busy
busy life. So I don't start to feel like
why do I walk so much? I know I don't
get to show you guys while I walk, but I
look crazy while I work cuz like
sometimes I'm like barely dressed. I
look crazy. I don't brush my hair.
[snorts]
I just get the work done and sometimes I
work hours. Like I was working on
Sunday. Actually, it was Saturday
evening and then I was working till like
3:00 a.m. I stepped out to my storage by
my house to pick up something at 3:00
a.m. And I realized I locked myself out.
And I locked myself out with my phone
and my two phones actually, my iPad, my
car keys.
That was a crazy experience because um I
have the security lock and then I forgot
to I think you have to charge it like
every 3 months. I forgot to charge it
and I just been using the key cuz it has
keys. It has key card. It has
fingerprint lock. It has actual keys. So
because I forgot to charge it, I haven't
had the time cuz I've just been up and
down. I've been using the key and then I
locked the key in the house and I have a
spare key but it was with my mom and my
mom was out of the country so I was like
okay I have to charge this thing now
[music] and I could charge it with a
power bank but I don't have a power
bank. [laughter]
This is 3:00 a.m. So I call my security
and then I tell him to that I want to
use his phone. I know my mom's number. I
know my dad's number and I know Doris's
number. So, I try to call Doris, she's
not picking up. I call, she's not
picking up. And then I call my mom who's
all the way out of the country, and she
picks up. And I'm like, "Yay, this is a
mother." You know, mothers are always
just going to be there for you. So, I
call my mom, and then I tell her to call
my boyfriend, and then he comes to pick
me up
around 4:00 a.m., guys, that was crazy.
And then he gets someone to help me
unlock my door. And then I'm back in my
house working around like 10:00 11:00
a.m. And then I walk from that time,
that's on Sunday, all the way all the
way all the way to 8:00 a.m. on Monday.
I didn't bite. I didn't sleep.
That's how many hours. 11:00 a.m. to
11:00 p.m. is already 12 hours. So 12:00
p.m. 1:00 a.m. 2:00 a.m. 3:00 a.m. 4:00
a.m. 5:00 a.m. 6:00 a.m. 7:00 a.m. 8:00
a.m. So I walked 21 hours, 21 hours
straight.
I didn't bat an eye. I didn't sleep. I
didn't nap. I only took eating breaks
and I was on with my comfort show.
Life with the water boys.
Gym instructor couldn't I couldn't make
it to the gym on Monday. So I saw him on
Tuesday. I was like, "I'm sorry I
couldn't make it on Monday. I was
working all through the night and even
when you came. I literally was not done
working so I couldn't make it." Um and
then you know what he told me? He was
like, "People that would look at you
would think your life is soft."
I didn't know how to feel when he said
that. He's like, "People that look at
you think your life is soft." Like, they
have no idea. Cuz he's the one who he he
understands that, okay, sometimes I'm in
the gym, I'm on my phone, I'm in the
gym, I'm getting calls, I'm in the gym,
I'm so weak, I can barely do much, but I
just still want to do something. I'm
like, I've been sitting for 12 hours
straight. to when we're doing our back
workout today, I can't squat because my
back is just going to break. He
understands, but I don't get to show a
lot of these things online because it's
like when I'm working, I'm locked in. I
don't just remember to set a camera and
start working. Like, it's just
I don't know, maybe I need to learn
that. But once again, I'm not trying to
look for, oh my god, Diana is so
hardworking. I ain't looking for that.
In fact, I rather be like, oh, she
doesn't do [\h__\h] She don't do [\h__\h] She
just she's just having fun. So yeah, DJ
is here. She's going to be spending the
day with me.
>> So we having IV pill.
>> Okay.
>> It will contain pretty iron and vitamin
C.
>> Also boost your immune also.
>> Okay.
>> Yep. Are you ready?
>> Yeah, I'm ready. I have like this
supplement. So I'm like hope it's not
going to be too much glow.
>> Now you're like, right, everybody.
[laughter]
Hi. Hi.
Good afternoon. How was work today? So,
how many hours do you think everything
will take after all?
>> So, your facials, let me confirm what
facials you're doing in particular, but
this should be 30 to 45 minutes.
>> Okay. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah.
[clears throat]
[music]
>> [music]
>> I think this [music and singing] one.
[music]
>> [music]
>> the actual swing.
>> Oh, yes.
[music]
>> [music]
>> So my confusion now is if a client wants
to switch [music] their book, is it for
him to shoot. I don't get it
cuz now we want to do how many [music]
looks and I want to add an extra look.
be found. You should take a look.
[music]
>> [snorts and music]
>> So this finish I just facial 1 hour with
massage [music]
[singing] peeling everything away with
the mask.
>> Okay.
>> And light moisturizer. [music]
>> All right. Thank you very much. Here you
go.
>> So guys, it's a wrap. We [music] did a
real nice glow facial. No extractions
cuz she says there's nothing to extract
[music] from the skin
and exfoliation and serums
and
>> [music]
>> princess around.
>> Bye.
Thank you.
So guys, we are headed to the spa,
another spa. I want to do my waxing.
I would have done everything at the same
place, but I don't cheat on where I do
my waxing. Like I always do it. I've
been going there for like 3 or 4 years
now, and I just don't cheat. Like the
way I do my facials here, I just like to
just when you know someone that does
something well for you, you just stick
with it because your skin is precious.
You don't know something a different
method might not just be especially when
it's close to your birthday, you don't
want to be trying new things. I'm even
so happy that we didn't do any
extractions on my face because a lot of
times when you do extractions, the area
is kind of poor. You kind of bruise and
I'm not ready for all that drama for my
birthday. So yeah, let's go get my
waxing done.
I'm actually so hungry. I took my
vitamins when I had not eaten. Crazy.
I'm also supposed to um meet with
Abdullah. Abdullah is now so popular.
Everybody knows Abdullah, but Abdalah
was my high school mate.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Maybe we should be going out. I don't
like this to do [\h__\h] like this.
>> I wish I had
this.
>> You don't know about the outside house?
>> No.
>> Hey, it's quite old.
>> Hi, welcome.
>> My sister, [music]
>> how are you?
>> Nigeria looks so good on you.
>> Thank you. It's my city. Of course,
>> the queen of Lagos.
>> Of course, you run.
>> Stop playing. The queen the bodies.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Wait a minute.
[music]
>> I decline.
>> Keep going. Keep going. Try hard.
[music] Keep going. Keep going. Keep
going.
[music]
>> Almost there. Almost.
Almost there. [music]
[music]
One more.
>> [cheering]
>> Come on.
Can I tell you?
[cheering]
[music]
Hey,
I want you
[music]
Heat. Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> That was the quickest shopping ever.
Guys, I'm about to get my lashes done.
They're the best. I mean, my lashes are
already done, so it's like, what am I
doing? It's just that my birthday's
coming, so I need new lashes. But these
lashes, they've been on for like 2
weeks, and they're still so pretty.
Like, I'm not going to take these off
now. I'm just going to do a refill cuz I
love how simple they are.
[music]
Yeah.
Hey, [music]
you know my friend is very mad at you.
[music] She's from the US. She came in
December.
Oh, I remember. I think she thought she
was booking you [music] directly because
that's why she actually thought that she
was booking you. [music] Sorry.
[laughter]
>> Pretend Sorry.
She come back. [music]
>> You want to You want to make it up to
her? [laughter]
>> Okay, I'll tell her. Got [music] my hair
done for my birthday shoot.
Trust the process.
I don't know why blonde is always scary
these days, especially when it's all
like ash. Like when it's yellow blonde,
it's like
we're semi done with the hair. Time for
my makeup.
Oh my god.
Wake up. Wake up. [music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> just received a tiny little badge for
everyone attending the launch. So,
they're going to be getting this first
time. If it gets sold out, everybody
else has to wait because me and stuff
have interacted. But I'm so happy that
this patch made it. I almost felt like
we're not going to be able to launch
this. But what can I say? God loves me.
God loves you, too, cuz you're going to
be getting access. So,
this took me nearly 2 years.
[music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hello.
So,
[music]
we just arrived the location [music]
for the shoot. May God grant us the best
shoot we've ever had. May everything go
well. May everybody be happy. Let
everything just be perfect. Like, may
God blow my mind with this shoot. Amen.
See you guys inside. [music]
Heat.
[music]
Heat. Heat. Heat. [music]
Yeah.
Heat.
Burn
it up.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
grateful. [music] You girls are so so
stunning. Like I can beat my chest and
say [music] that members of my community
are the most beautiful girls. So yeah,
clock it.
>> Today we get to some celebration.
So today I finally get to share um
Glazer and Glossy with you guys. And
>> [music]
>> um these might just look like products,
but they've taken so much time for me to
actually launch them. I was ensuring
that the launch made sense. I was trying
to put things together to make sure that
everything was quality because in this
community, we don't settle for less.
>> So finally, I get to introduce Glazer
and Glossy to you guys. I get to share
it with you all. Um, so with Glazer, we
have five different shades. I've been
using them for over a year now, and you
know, I kind of understand the [music]
best ways to use them. This is Glazer
Berry. She's that berry pink. You know,
everybody loves a nice pink blush. Like,
this is [music] like the blush that
doesn't go wrong. So, I could give it a
little swatch. This is a girly girly
makeup space. [music] So, it's this
shade. It's pink. It's hot pink. It's
pigmented. You'll [snorts] always catch
me having it on my cheeks, especially
when I want to step out [music] cuz it's
Barry just screams, "Yes, I'm here." You
know, she's a showstopper. And today, I
packed Berry with her thief. Shout out
to my models actually. They're in the
house. She's one of them. And I can't
find the other two, but they're
somewhere. They're somewhere in the
house. They're somewhere in the house.
So, today for my makeup look, I paired
Earthy with berry. So, I find that
Earthy is kind of like a warm brown,
warm orange um blush. So, most of the
time I use it as a bronzer. I put it on
the contours of my face. It gives me
that warmth to my makeup. You know, a
lot of times when you do your makeup
with powders and all that, you start
looking too white and too bright. And
sometimes you want to have that tan
look. You know, not like your sunburnt,
but like you're tan. And I absolutely
love a tan look. If you know me, you
know that Earthy was created to do that.
Today I paired earthy with berry for my
>> and you guys can tell it's stunning,
right?
>> Be honest.
>> Be honest. So yeah, that's what I paired
for my makeup look today and I
absolutely love them. These are not just
cheek blushes though. They also for your
lips. So they're the one item you can
put in your handbag and just
and you can wear them without makeup.
That's the [music] best part. You don't
have to have a full face of makeup to
wear these. You can literally just wear
them without makeup. That is the most
amazing part for me because I take into
consideration my giries that are still
learning how to beat their face and all
that because when I started this brand,
I didn't know how to do my makeup. So,
most of the products that we launch also
half of the girls that don't really know
how to do like the full face of makeup
and you still want to have that cute
chic look. If you go on my social media,
you've noticed I've done a lot of 5
minute makeup looks with these. So, you
can check those out. I've noticed from
the testers, people don't know that when
you wind it up, you can wind it down.
So, that's how it goes. So, if you want
to wind it up, you can wind it up. You
can wind it down. And when you want to
keep it, just make sure you wind it down
because it's a cream product. So, yeah.
Up next, I like to call them the twins.
I call them the twins because they
actually look similar, but they're not
the same. So this is sassy and this is
savvy. The difference between these two
is this is cool tone and this is warm
tone. So you know the girls who have
been digging it into their makeup and
their skin care, they can tell you, "Oh,
I'm warm tone. Oh, I'm yellow tone." Or
I'm still not on that level yet. But you
know, these blushes are actually very
similar, but they're not the same. She's
called Sassy. What I like about this is
[music] she doubles as that bright pink
blush and she also works as [music] a
lip base for your lip combo. So say you
want to do a nice lip combo, you just
apply this, put your lip liner, put your
lip gloss and you find that it lasts
longer than just putting on your lip
gloss and your lip [music] pencil
because you have a base. So that's
literally what I use these two for.
They're kind of like my transition
blushes as well. [music] So you know, am
I speaking too much English? You guys
know transition. You don't CHANGE SO
MUCH, RIGHT? OH, YEAH. I TRUST I TRUST
my girls. I know my girls. I know my
girls know what's up. So, I usually
transition from this to this. So, I put
this like here and then I put this like
because this is more bold. So, if I want
something that's a little, you know,
soft, I go for sassy or I go for Savvy.
Peachy is actually so iconic because
she's the kind of blush that you be
like,
are you sure you're going to try this
blush? Pitch is bright. She is peach.
And you know, like I always say, the
girls that get it, get it. And it's
fine. It's it's absolutely fine. If you
get it, you get it. If you don't get it,
you go for THE ONES THAT YOU GET. YOU
GET ME? So yeah, peachy is that [music]
peach tone blush. And most of the time
what I use peachy for. I have peachy on
today, but I also have glossy on, but
we're going to get there. So my lip
combo today is this is the base. I use
peachy as my base. I was going to post
on my Instagram stories, but I'm like,
"Oh my goodness, I'm running late. I
don't want these girls to think that
they shouldn't start doing their makeup.
So, I decided to come here first, but
I'll post about all of it later. So,
this is the base I have on today. And I
paired it with a lip gloss. Peachy is
iconic. She's that iconic Peach. There
was this era of Peach Nudes. I don't
know if Well, I'm actually so young,
too. So, I were all so young, but that
era of Peach Nude, I was such a little
girl and I was obsessed with it. So,
that's why I had to incorporate that
into the Glazer collection. And um yeah,
that's the full glazer collection. Five
shades. What do you guys think?
>> Which one? Which one are you going to be
rooting for? LIKE
>> IF WE'RE ALL FOR BARRY, say yeah.
>> If we're all for Sassy, say yeah.
[laughter]
>> If we're all for Sabi, SAY YEAH. YEAH.
>> OKAY. OKAY.
>> YEAH. IF WE'RE UP for say Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. I see the girls. I see what
the girls love. And you guys need to
catch on peachy, TOO. IF YOU'RE ON FOR
PEACHY, SAY YEAH. YEAH.
[laughter]
That's it for the glazer collection.
Now, let's get to glossy. So, let me
give you guys a little secret, [music]
right? You guys are actually the first
people to experience Glossy.
This limited stock literally landed
yesterday. That's why you noticed that
there are no names on them yet because I
wanted you guys to experience these
glosses as they landed. I didn't want to
waste no time. I promised you guys a
special launch and I said I'm going to
do this. So, yes, let's get to the
glossy collection. This is about to be
your new obsession. So, get ready.
>> Get ready. Take my word for it. you
ready?
>> So, let's start with her. She's actually
called Rude. And the inspiration behind
her being called Rude is We also have um
our TC lip glosses. We have a similar
shade called Mean. And I find that, you
know, those girls that really want to
give bad, [music] like, I don't have too
many words to say to you. Like, I'm not
going to even smile at you. [music]
Like, I'm just too I'm too cool for
everybody. That's what this gloss is. Um
I'm just going to swatch as well because
I really don't mind. It's makeup. That's
how we play. So she is that um golden
brown shade and she also has shimmers
inside of her. Um now let me tell you
something about this particular gloss.
This was 2 years in the making.
Two whole years in the making. You know
why? Because I kept on learning and
unlearning things. Tomorrow I find out
that, oh my god, there are lip glosses
that are peptide infused. I'm like, no,
the lip gloss I launched for my Shine
Girls [music] have to be peptide
infused. And then I hear, oh, there's
SPF lip glosses. I'm like, no. In fact,
my production company at some point they
were mad at me like, come on, how many
things do you want to add? How many
things do you want to change? Like,
let's just launch this. I was like, no,
please, let's add this. I will pay extra
money. I need I fought for this to be as
perfect as it is. So, I'm so happy to
introduce it to you girls. Um, it's
vitamin E infused. In fact, let me just
read out so that you hear.
>> This is first of all, it says obviously
I'm a star [music] because you guys are
stars and you guys know my obviously
word. So, you know, I had to share that.
I had to extend that. So, obviously
whenever you use this, you remember that
I'm a star. Mhm. So, it's a peptide
infused lip treatment that delivers
intense [music] hydration. It has
antioxidants. Are you guys listening?
>> It has antioxidants and it has shea
butter. It has kalow butter. It has
vitamin C and E. It has SPF [music] 20.
So, you know, a lot of people complain
that sometimes when they wear lip
glosses, they notice that their lips get
sunburned. And I got some complaints
about that. I'm like, "Oh, okay. There
has to be some solution around this."
So, we had to make sure that these have
SPF. So, while you're protecting your
face, cuz I know the whole campaign
about sunscreen, it's loud. I mean, we
all use sunscreen, right?
>> Yes. So, now we have a lip care product
that doesn't just, you know, make us
look pretty. It also has health
benefits. [clears throat] It protects
us. It has so many beautiful benefits.
It heals us. So, while you're wearing
your lip gloss and you're looking all
pretty, you're also getting healed,
you're getting vitamins. Like, please
give me a round of applause.
[applause and cheering]
So, yeah, this is the shade rouge. And
yeah, she's that girl. Now, let's get to
the shade. Basically, they have the same
things infused. They just have different
shades. [music] And they smell so good.
Has anybody noticed? No.
>> Have you guys tested them out? They
smell so so good. I see the girl saying,
"Ooh, like you guys are feeling it,
right?" I'm just thinking of myself
stepping out like an evening out or
dinner. [music] Then I just have this on
and I'm just sparkling and I'm just
feeling like the only girl in the
[singing] world.
So yeah, these glosses have their own
personalities. No, she has that light
pink tint that is not going to make your
lips look like they are blown out pink
or blown out whitish pink. They have
this. Actually, there's a lip gloss I
used to use as a child that I absolutely
loved that even inspired me to start up
my makeup brand and it was this shade.
So, I decided that when I'm launching
Glossy, I had to bring that back cuz I
have to share my passions with my girls.
So, let's get to the next one. Hm. All
the girls here are already raving about
this one. It's like this is going to be
our bests seller. But let's see. She's
called Bratz and she is [music]
she's just literally she's a Bratz doll.
Let me show you.
>> Do you see that? Do you see that? You
see that shade of pink? So, I mean the
girlies already know Kiss. Our Kiss
gloss is like our bestseller. Everybody
knows Kiss. So, this is kind of like
Kiss, but she has this pink shimmer in
her that gives her this I don't know
this special.
I don't have words to describe Bratz,
but you know, I think she might be my
favorite, but I don't want to pick
favorites. I'm a good I'm a good mom to
all. I don't I don't want to do that.
But yeah, this is Bratz. And she is that
cute hot pink that you always want to
have in your handbag.
Up next, Bob, right? Is this Bab? Where
is Joy?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh lord, I'm a little confused now
because she's shining like Anyway, I
told them that they should make sure
that this set is shiny. Like, we need to
be entering people's eyes. Can you see
that?
>> That's one swipe. Now I'm even confused.
I'm like, okay. Yeah, it's sheer, but it
has shimmer. Yeah. Up next.
Okay, this was the first one we tried.
Oh yeah, this is the last but not the
least and her name is Hottie. And you're
going to agree that she is a hottie.
So let's give her a swatch.
So yeah.
>> Yes. So she's kind of similar to the
cherry that we already have, but she's
very different. She has her own
personality and she's a hottie. So yeah,
these are the I mean except this this
was a blush. So we swatched out all of
the lip gloss [music] shades and we
tried to make sure that everyone's going
to find something that they like. Oh, I
don't really like pink.
Then there's there's the clear
shimmerred ones, you know. Oh, I don't
really like the the clear shimmered
ones. There's [music] a one that has a
little hint of light pink that's not so
hot pink. Oh, I don't like light pink. I
like [music] hot pink. We have hot pink
for you. Oh, I just like brown lip
glosses. Like that's all I wear. We have
rude. So everything for everybody. It's
enough to go around. I'm just going to
just run through our products that you
guys already know. Um this is our
lithology. You know, I don't think
anybody had done this before. Had
anybody put together a collection like
this before? I hadn't seen it before,
though. I'm like, you know, I have to do
the best for my shine girls. You guys
have to be feeling yourselves. Like you
know the thing is a lot of times people
try to make us feel like oh you're from
Nigeria.
Oh what goes on in that country? That's
why I make sure that whatever I'm
bringing to my country is the same
standard as whatever another celebrity
is bringing to the US or to the UK or
[music] to Canada. I make sure that we
don't do substandard over here no matter
what because my shine babes are quality
babes. [music]
And then we have a heart mirror.
my favorite products from my brand
because it's a mirror. I mean, I can
just
[laughter]
I could just, you know, adore myself and
I just feel like whenever I look at her,
it's like I'm saying I love you because
she's in the shape of a heart. So, yeah.
And then we have our lip glosses over
there. We have our beauty sponges over
here. And I think that's pretty much it.
I think that's that's enough of the
talking. I hope you guys have an amazing
time. We also have cocktails coming in.
And if you have any questions, does
anybody have any questions?
Any questions?
Any questions about the products?
Everything is pretty much clear. It's
like ABC. So anyway, if you have any
other extra questions you want to ask me
about makeup or about anything else,
feel free to ask me. I'm here for you
guys today. Like,
>> I have a question.
>> Oh, yeah, sure.
>> What's your favorite lip combo?
>> My favorite lip combo? That's going to
be very very [clears throat] hard
because I used to have previous favorite
lip combos, but now that we have five
different shades, I'll be having like 1
million lip combos. Prepare to be sick
of me. But currently, like the one that
I wear often is I always use this as my
base and then I use any other um gloss
over it. I love doll gloss when I'm
going out. I love Kiss gloss for every
when I wake up in the morning, I'm going
to bed. Sometimes my kiss gloss is
staining my pillow because I wear gloss
to go to bed. So kiss gloss is my life.
So I can't really I can't really rate
kiss with the other ones. I can't that's
that's going to be disrespectful. But
yeah. Um I can't really tell. But do I
have a favorite lip combo?
>> Yes. I think that's kind of like what
I'm wearing. I always like to have like
something like a nude base [music]
and then a brown lip. Makes my lips look
plum. and she doesn't look like I
actually have like a lip liner on. But
when I want to look like I have a lip
liner on, I go for mocha. And when I
want to show people that yes, I'm bad, I
go for rouge. And you know these other
two shades, I mostly use them as a base
for my lip combos. Yes. Because these
lip liners last. [music] Exactly. So
they last. So when you use a lip liner
for your base as well, it also ensures
that your lip combo stays in place all
day. And I can guarantee you that these
lip liners when you use them, you don't
have to reapply them. They don't run
away. What what's like what the heck is
lip liner is my lip liner is
disappearing. Like please, we don't do
that over here. So yeah, please enjoy
yourselves. And does anybody else have a
question?
>> I have one.
>> OKAY. NOW ONE PERSON ASKED NOW
EVERYBODY'S NOW LIKE YES, let me that's
that's okay. So what's your question? So
for um someone that she's not very fond
of makeup or do makeup or wants to use
your products especially this glazer you
said that is like a multiple in one can
like layer it glazer for this or how how
like how can someone that doesn't want
to do a full face makeup.
>> You don't want to do a full face makeup.
So let me teach you my hack. So now
there are two hacks you can use. My
friend Tai doesn't wear makeup on her
dayto-day, but she always wears this
blush and she just puts it on her cheeks
and on her lips and it works. I have
videos on my page. I even tell you to go
easy cuz this particular shade very
pigmented. Very pigmented. But if you
want to do it the way I do it. Ah, I
need to show you my phone. Where is my
phone? So there's this particular look I
usually create where I only wear
concealer and blush and powder and it
looks like I have a full face of makeup.
So what I do is I put my concealer under
my eyes. I put my blush at the
perimeters of my face. I extend my blush
to even my forehead. [music]
Like today my makeup artist did my
makeup saying I put blush on my forehead
please. Like I like I like looking all
rosy and cheeky. So yeah, I put the
concealer, I put the blush, and I put
powder. And it just gives me that no
makeup makeup look. You know, sometimes
you don't want to look caked.
>> You don't want to look like, oh, there's
powder on my face. So, you know, because
Lagos people, there's a difference
between one bed makeup and everyday
makeup. So, actually, this that I'm
wearing now, it's in between full glam
and, you know, subtle. But my dayto-day
makeup, you can literally almost see my
skin through it. But it just gives that
beautiful subtle finesse. So those days
I don't wear foundation. I just wear the
blush, put concealer, put powder, and
you look good. I have tutorials about
that on my Instagram. So you can do well
to check it out. Thank you.
>> You're welcome. Who else had a question?
Okay.
>> How long did it take for you like
perfect?
>> You know something about makeup. The
more you do your makeup.
>> Yes, that is it. I've actually seen one
of your makeup videos, so I know that
you know what's up. So please don't be
humble. Don't be humble around here, you
know. So, yeah, that's the thing about
makeup. The more you do it, if somebody
told me that I would know how to do my
makeup, I would have been like, cuz when
my mates were learning makeup, I was
like, "No, I don't like makeup. I'M
FINE. I'M FINE WITHOUT MAKEUP.
[screaming]
I don't need makeup." But the thing is,
don't do makeup because you don't think
you're beautiful. You do makeup because
it's a time where you connect to
yourself. You drop your things and you
focus on connecting. I feel like makeup
is therapy because I sit Yes, it's
therapy. I SIT DOWN AND I'M JUST doing
stuff. It's like I'm playing like I'm
doing artworks with myself. So, yes,
it's not about where people be like,
"Oh, but you're beautiful. You don't
have to wear makeup." It's not about I I
feel beautiful without makeup. But it's
fun. And what is life without a little
fun, you know?
>> You know, so yeah. Any other questions?
>> I have one.
>> Sure. Throw it.
>> Um, what product to your glosses? What
products do you recommend for a dark
skin like me?
>> Okay, so the thing is every see it's
just if am I a dark skin that likes to
play cool or am I a dark skin that's
like no let me not use the f word guys
sensor that please
>> I like to be cool.
>> Yeah. So like if you're playing it cool,
playing it chic.
Where is she? I'm trying to find her. I
think she she's gone already. We had a
lady from Ghana and she literally tried
this on. She has this beautiful dark
skin. She tried this on and she was
obsessed with it. It looked so so good
on her. So, I say she tried this one if
you want to play it safe or keep it cute
and chic. Berry is your girl. And I know
the gloss that you tried on today,
Bratz. You know that Bratz is your
thing. I don't have to
>> I don't have to say much. Bratz is Bratz
is that girl. But you see the thing with
all these lip glosses, it's just based
off preference. They are made for all
the skin tones. They not made
specifically for any skin. They work for
everybody. That's why you see with our
launch, [music] we have videos of ladies
with different skin tones trying on
these blushes. Obviously, we haven't
even done that for this because they
just came yesterday. I said we're going
to have them here today. [music] So,
yeah. Any other questions?
>> Anybody? Anybody? Anybody? Cuz we need
to get back to the music and dancing.
So, are you ready to get back to the
music?
>> All right, let's bring it on, Mr. DJ.
Thank you guys for having me. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> I love that.
[music]
How many
>> [music]
>> It's your huge
[music]
>> I think it looks really good. Your
outfit.
>> I love it.
>> [music]
>> How do I
[music]
feel?
>> [music]
[music]
>> You make
>> [music]
>> Please
[music]
help me.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Diane.
Diane.
Diana knows
[music]
>> a so [music] cute. [singing]
A
[music]
>> thank you.
>> Hold on.
[music]
Thank you. [music]
Hey guys, everything. [music]
[music]
No, but I was going to [music] do it.
Oh, this game has very close.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hello.
[music]
[singing]
Say hello to these green.
Oh,
[music]
wow. [music]
>> [music]
>> Guys, [music] we have how many bouquets?
Wow.
And it's not even my birthday [music]
yet.
These are huge.
Wow. Wow.